Man of God, help me, I have cancer.
I have taken one but I have to take one more.
Man of God, please help my husband. He has cancer.
He has taken one; it is remaining one and the doctors said it is fifty – fifty.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for Mr Grytli.
This is prayer in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Watch as this man moves against his will,
there is a force busy at work setting him free, in the mighty, all-powerful name of Jesus Christ.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Healing And Deliverance In Jesus’ Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Good Morning, Church!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Geir Grytli, I am from Norway.
The woman beside me is my lovely wife - Princess.
In 2016 I got cancer in my thyroids.
There was a lot of pain and I couldn't do anything.
We were watching Emmanuel TV all the time because operation is not a solution.
Having watched Emmanuel TV, we decided to come here, to The SCOAN.
We came here in June 2017.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me - I fell down and I felt cold.
When we came back to Norway, we ministered the Morning Water in the mornings and evenings.
After some time I went back to the hospital; they took an ultrasound and they couldn't find any cancer.
I'm free, I'm strong.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ; put your hands beautifully for the miracle-working God.
Trust in God; He will do it.
Hallelujah!
You heard it - trust in God, He will do it.
No other one can do it, except Jesus Christ.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Princess Grytli, I come from Norway.
The man beside me is my husband.
My husband got cancer in 2016.
It was so severe that he couldn't do anything at all.
The doctor said it was fifty - fifty.
I said that it was not a lottery to leave his body to "fifty - fifty".
In 2017, we came to The SCOAN.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for my husband; he fell down, he felt cold.
After we went back to Norway, we ministered the Morning Water in the mornings and evenings.
After we ministered it, my husband went back to the hospital;
they checked him and said there was no more cancer.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Here is the medical report that I had a cancer of 2,7 centimetres in my thyroids,
and here is the confirmation from my doctor that there is no more cancer in my body.
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus!
My word of advice to all viewers and those here in the auditorium is to trust in God.
When you trust in God, all other things will be added to you, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
TT Robert Begier 19/04/2019
RV: Mel Flowers 19/04/2019